m4maths.com 2016-06-08

# M4maths Privacy policy

### M4MATHS Privacy Policy

We at **M4MATHS** are committed to respecting your privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (any information by which you can be identified, such as address, email, and telephone number). That is why **M4MATHS** has established this privacy policy, so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information.

We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. 

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles: 

## INFORMATION

We want to give you information about our privacy policy and assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that it is followed within our site. 

## EMAIL

**M4MATHS** does not engage in or support spamming or misuse of email addresses. 

We require your email address when you register as a member to our Site. Your email address is used once to send you a welcome notice, and may be used to send The mail such as a major change to our service, Weekly result, or to send your password if you lose/forget it and mail if your friend invite you to join the site. If you take part in our contests, and are a winner, your prize notification will also be sent at that address. Any other emails from **M4MATHS** will only be sent to you if you explicitly ask us to send them.  
m4maths can send you email related to m4maths or its other product(iitbrain, 0mrp). If you don't want to get any promotional email then you can un-subscribe for email. 

When you use the "invite your friend" feature on the **M4MATHS** web site, the email address of your friend is used only to send your invitation mail with your message. No further emails are sent to that address, nor is that address revealed to any third party. 

Your email address is held in strict confidence, and only used as stated here. 

## ACCURACY

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you to review and update your information in the future.

## SECURITY

We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

## COOKIES

Third party vendors, including Google, media.net and other ad networks use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. You can also check http://www.aboutads.info/ on how to opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising 

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. For more information on how Google uses data when you use our partner’ sites or apps, visit this link: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/ 

## SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

**M4MATHS** may share aggregate information about its users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, we may say **M4MATHS** audience is x percent from one country or state and y percent from other country or state. This data is used to customize the content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

##  Links to Other Sites

**M4MATHS** contains links to other sites. Please be aware that M4MATHS.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the **M4MATHS** Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the **M4MATHS** Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

##  Advertising and 3rd party ads

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.  
Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.)  
If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy as well in the following manner.

Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.  
Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.  
Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.  
Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative for guidance on drafting a privacy policy.

**Thank you for your support of these policies and of M4MATHS.com.**
